Register of the Julius Epstein Papers, 1939-1975
Hoover Institution Archives
- PHOTOGRAPHS., August, 1939; (17 prints / 1 envelope (Box 75063 - 10.A-V Envelope mA)
  17 prints relating to the signing of the non-aggression pact between Germany and the Soviet Union. Includes one print depicting Hitler.